[Music: ‘He’s a Black Flame Dragon’ theme song]
(Juyeon) What is the name of the store?
I thought it was somewhere I knew.
(Edited) Write it down, you probably don’t know?
Maybe it's because I'm a bit isolated
Strangely, there are no customers.
It tastes good
Are you sure?
Because it’s not easy to suit my taste
Then go home and eat.
I'll go alone
Let's go first.
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Sparkling sound effect]
[Exciting music]
Oh, can I do that?
to win me
How hard have you worked?
Isn’t that what the general manager has to say?
[Soft music]
Done
[Sparkling sound effect]
(Hajin) Oh my, oh my, what should I do, what should I do
Quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly
[Call connection tone]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Sujeong clears her throat in embarrassment]
Uh, sister, right in front of me...
don't come
- (Edited) Huh?
- (Hajin) Don’t ever come.
There's a black flame dragon here!
[Heavy sound effect]
[upbeat music]
[Sujeong’s heavy breathing]
(Juyeon) What are you doing?
(Edit) That...
Black at the store...
Black...
(Juyeon) Black?
[Sujeong’s embarrassed breathing]
It's dark history.
[humorous music]
(Edited) The scammer who scammed me in the game
The biggest black story of my life
I can't find it with my own feet.
So you're saying you ran away?
If anyone sees it, it's Baek Soo-jeong.
I think you're a scammer
(Juyeon) I’d rather take this opportunity
I'll scold you, let's go.
(Edited) Oh, no!
[Surprise] My first love...
That's first love
Not just a scammer
I don't want to see you again
I don't even want to see it.
(Juyeon) That heart
I know too
I know
This posture is a bit...
(Edited) Ah...
[Exciting music]
Oh, sorry
I didn't do that on purpose.
Ah...
You thought it was a wall
Why is my chest so firm...
Is it something else?
Did you just exercise instead of doing that?
Of course I did both
(Juyeon) Try comparing something
Do it in moderation
Moderately
It's an adverb that isn't in my dictionary.
(Juyeon) So are you going to keep hiding?
What should I do if I run into him when I go out?
(Juyeon) What does he look like?
- yes?
- You have to know what it looks like to avoid it.
I don't know
(Edited) I saw it briefly when I was very young.
Wow, your face must have changed a lot.
Then even if we meet
You don't recognize me, do you?
[surprised] That’s right
(Juyeon) Someone passed by earlier
(Edited) Did you go?
(Hajin) So
Yeomryong is
Are you saying that Sujeong is the head of the division?
Oh my, what should I do?
[surprised sigh]
(Edit) I can take the bus from here.
Let’s go in first.
[Sound of bus door opening]
[Card recognition sound]
[Soft music]
[Sound of bus door closing]
[Clears cough]
Weren’t you going to the company?
How many times do you take the bus?
Number 770
Would you please wait?
Well, it will come soon
[shocked breathing]
(Edited) Ah
I picked it up at the arcade.
He seems like my favorite character
Why?
Is it too touching?
Well, who told the general manager
I'll give you a gift, I'll give it to you
There's nothing to be too thankful for.
(Juyeon) It’s not that I’m thankful.
Can't you tell just by looking at it?
[Humorous sound effects]
It's a counterfeit product that hasn't been authenticated.
[humorous music]
What are Muggle eyes?
And this
Not just a character, but a joke
Tokeeng, Tokeeng
This is definitely a friend with a name.
Oh, don't hate it.
[Dodging sound effect]
(Main role) Baek Soo-jeong
I will accept it out of courtesy.
[bright music]
Then
take care
[Sound of bus door opening]
Yes, I will go.
(Junsu) Yesterday’s headquarters meeting
You said it wasn't a joke?
Everything is taken away, just the team leader
I heard you survived. Is this true?
Yeah, well...
(Junsu) Hello?
[Sounds of employees greeting each other]
[Refreshing music]
(Edited) As you can see, the current food hall is
Focusing on high-quality food
Diversity and accessibility
The opinion is that it is falling.
In order to secure new customers
Popular brands on SNS
It is urgent to attract
It's not enough to just be popular.
At a competing department store right next door
It must be a brand that cannot be found
So I narrowed it down
This is a list of companies, Director.
It's good
I guess we can proceed like this.
yes
(Main role) Food and beverages
In terms of customer attraction or sales
These are all important parts
It will be a key point of the renewal project.
please take care
Skills in this kind of work
You can prove it
Don't disappoint this time
[Door bell sounds]
[Sujeong’s satisfied moan]
(Edited) It's been rough since the morning.
So?
What the hell is that kid?
Why did you suddenly come to the store?
- That's...
- (Surrender) Are you saying we won’t meet each other?
You said you only contacted me occasionally?
It's true, but it suddenly appears
Oh, I'm in trouble too, I'm in trouble
How should I do this?
I was in trouble too, I was in trouble.
(Edited) I took the general manager with me.
I can't even eat
(Hajin) So
When did you become so close to the head of the department?
They said I was a funny idiot
I guess he’s no longer a fool?
Ah, well...
[Sound of putting down a cup]
As I've been living
It was better than you thought?
Are you okay?
[Clears cough]
You mean
If Yeomryong
[Interesting music]
I became a good person like that general manager.
So what do you think?
What does that mean?
What do these two have to do with each other?
So if
So
How can he become a decent person?
I was yellow from the beginning.
(Edited) Well, even if he suddenly received the Nobel Prize
To me it's the same scammer
What's different?
Do you want to change jobs?
Why do you keep saying something different?
that bastard shop
Are you doing this because you don’t want them to come?
I really didn't make you come
Then who told you to come?
[cell phone vibrating sound]
uh?
(Edited) Strange
Why is there no answer, huh?
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Sujeong clears her throat]
Yes, manager.
Oh, haven't you changed your password yet?
[Laughing] Yes, look.
I told you to change it quickly.
yes, i understand
I have urgent business at work.
I have to go in and see.
Talk to you later, okay?
[sigh]
[Door bell sounds]
Why is it so urgent?
(Hajin)
[ding sound effect]
[Bounce sound effect]
[Sound effect of pointing]
[Humorous sound effects]
(Shinwon) Pan!
[Exciting music]
Director
Let's go together, okay?
[Humorous sound effects]
Are you two close?
Mr. Hajin?
How does Mr. Hajin get here?
[surprised gasp]
[Shinwon’s embarrassed exclamation]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Shinwon’s embarrassed laughter]
Oh, this is a company.
Did you come to see me?
From the answer
Are you two close?
(Shinwon) Yes?
Ah, yes
(Hajin) How much?
[Shinwon’s embarrassed sigh]
A lot, a lot, a lot, a lot
Then, do you know his first love?
(Shinwon) Oh, you can’t know that.
Jooyeon’s first love is
Because it’s a curse and an evil
Until now
Hey, banjuyeon
Honestly, you want to play too
Aren’t grades important anyway?
A day like today is stressful
I have to release it to maintain that grade.
Let's play a game with my brother, okay?
What game should we play?
cart? Maple? star?
[Exciting music]
Me that
(Shinwon) Hey
Come visit my brother too.
After all, we only have Panjju, huh?
[Sound of door closing]
[light laughter]
What happened to what I said?
(Young lead character) Chicken?
Fried, seasoned
Hey, thank you
(Shinwon) Please eat this, please eat this
[Soldiers cheering]
(Soldier) Good!
[Shinwon’s happy laughter]
But bro
(Shinwon) Huh?
me
I'm going to confess to strawberry
[Interesting music]
Awesome
How do I confess?
How did you confess?
I just took it
I've never done it before
(Shinwon) Hey, just relax
Anyway, rather than the method
Because the heart is important
no, and
so cool
Yongseong's successor confesses
What kind of woman rejects you?
Ugh
Ugh, snob.
Strawberry doesn't know who I am
This country's existence itself
I just like it
When we date
Do I really need to tell my brother?
(Shinwon) When I fight, my brother
I'll give you 200 won
Tutu?
[Shinwon’s sigh]
[Shinwon takes a breath]
[Call connection tone]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Voice guidance) This is a collect call.
Check the other person
(Shinwon) Uh, Panjju, it’s your brother.
Uh, don't hang up, don't hang up
Why?
(Shinwon) Ah, why?
Unfortunately, I haven't heard from my brother.
Because you're busy dating strawberry
Have you forgotten your brother?
never again
(Shinwon) Huh?
Don't ever mention that name again
What, why?
Did you really get dumped?
(ID) No, why? What the hell
What are you lacking?
[Sad music]
Hey, what's the problem?
my very existence
They say that existence itself is extremely repulsive
How can you say such harsh words...
Don't contact me in the future either.
I won't do anything useless anymore
[Call end sound]
Hey, hey, hey, Panjju, Panjju, don't hang up, don't hang up
(Shinwon) It will be from then on.
Juyeon, who seemed like my age for a moment
Yongseong's perfect successor again
The reason I only focused on what was possible was
conglomerate heir
(Hajin) Aliens
I'm glad I'm not a gangster
(Shinwon) Yes?
Ah, anyway
That's what my first love gave me
It was a big wound.
Why do you lie about your age like that?
[Exciting music]
(Hajin) Do you know how surprised I was when I saw it during Jeongmo?
(Shinwon) No matter how much I lied about my age, it’s true
The very existence is so disgusting
Oh, that's too harsh.
Even if it were me, I would have been hurt.
(Hajin) How dare you say that?
Oh my gosh
(Shinwon) Bad is bad, indeed
(Hajin) No...
[Hajin’s absurd moans]
(Shinwon) Huh?
Who is the really bad one?
[absurd elasticity]
Is this really our main character?
Then, shall we fix it?
[sigh]
(Shinwon) It’s okay.
Well, we'll never meet again anyway.
Of course, if we meet again
[Interesting music]
Due to the main character's personality
A person who left a stain on one's life
I won't leave you alone
do whatever it takes
[Humorous sound effects]
Because they'll try to block your path
First in Korea
It's certain that I can't live.
no
[Taking a breath] At the company I worked for
Are you going to start by kicking them out?
[Sound effect pops up]
What a terrible and scary kid he is.
[Sparkling sound effect]
It must be hard to handle, right?
Why are you so shocked?
[Surprise] Oh, were you too scared?
The scary thing is Sujeong.
[Exciting music]
(Hajin) If it’s the crystal I know
Embarrassment, shame, and disgrace suffered by oneself
I'll try to pay it all back
[Humorous sound effects]
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth
I'm a child with iron rules in life.
It's hard to live in Korea
Will it be Sujeong?
Jooyeon might have a hard time living on Earth?
Ah, then
Mr. Sujeong
As much as Juyeon
Are you saying it’s terrible?
The Sujeong I know is
yes
[Shinwon’s embarrassed exclamation]
(Shinwon) Because the two of you have no reason to meet
I'm so glad
What if we need to meet up?
- yes?
- What if we already meet every day?
[sound of a switch being pressed]
[lively music]
(Juyeon) Now...
[Humorous sound effects]
[Exciting music] (Shinwon) No
The crystal I mentioned so far
Are you Baek Soo-jeong, the team leader?
Headquarters killer?
Ah, but why is it so quiet?
- no way...
- Yes
We don't recognize each other
(Shinwon) Wow...
That's a relief
Actually
It was so long ago
I think we only met briefly
It's too early to be at ease
(Hajin) The two have become quite close.
The atmosphere is also unusual.
Getting this close
If we even feel each other as opposite sex
(Shinwon) Then later
If you find out his identity...
[Flying sound effect]
(Shinwon, Hajin) It’s terrible!
I need to drop it right away.
I won't be able to find out for the rest of my life!
[anxious sigh]
[Elevator arrival sound]
[Elevator button sound]
[Sound of approaching footsteps]
[Card recognition sound]
[Sound of gate opening]
[Shinwon’s embarrassed exclamation]
[light music]
[Shinwon sighs in relief]
(Juyeon) What are you doing?
why? I have to go up quickly
You are busy every minute and every second.
[light laughter]
But that Baek Soo-jeong
I did a little more research and
Why did you do such a useless thing?
I told you it was okay to stop.
[Interesting music]
Well, I think I did my research too roughly at the time.
(Shinwon) Oh, so I tried it.
I'm stronger than I thought
It seemed terrible
Wouldn't it be inconvenient to work together?
So you said you think I would be a good match?
(Shinwon) There was another problem, uh
I was wondering if there was a man interested in the company.
A guy you're interested in?
Uh, there's a guy I'm interested in.
You absolutely hate male relationships.
(Shinwon) Don’t get involved with people from the company.
You asked me to take care of you and even warned you.
But is it okay or something like that, um
well
[Swallows saliva]
[Exciting music]
He's a man I'm interested in...
No way...
[Sparkling sound effect]
[Laughing] Me?
That's difficult
[Happy laughter]
[Sound of people murmuring]
[Interesting music]
[Door bell sounds]
sister
Are you here? Where would you like to sit?
[Humorous sound effects]
[Winking sound effect]
(Hajin) Sujeong-ah
Oh my
You can't sit here, can you?
(Edited) Ah, I will come out when guests arrive.
Ah...
So, what's there to say?
(Edited) No way, those men
You're not going to introduce me, are you?
(Hajin) Uhm
[Printer operating sound]
[Messenger notification sound]
(Hajin) What do you do after work today?
Are you going home right away?
Don't work overtime
(Edited) Why is this happening?
Are you very bored because of lack of business?
He said it was okay
[Seokhee’s urgent groan]
(Seokhee) The logo draft was released.
I printed it
(Junsu) Oh
Oh, that's nice, what about me?
This is what we thought
I think it feels the same
Um, sure
It's the first draft, but it was chosen well.
- (Edit) Almost no need to edit
- (Junsu) Yes
(Nana) Wow...
Wow, as expected, Director Kim is the best.
no, how
Everything is so perfect, right?
I'm really going crazy
[laughter]
Nana?
(Junsu) Oh, Nana was like this too.
Would you like to join the fan club?
A fan club?
(Junsu) No, to our company
There is a fan club for Chief Kim.
Was Assistant Manager Jeong of the design department the chairman?
Anyway, I guess so.
Is it that popular?
(Nana) Of course
Hey, the director, you’re so cool.
Be kind and smile a lot
Kind and good manners
How do you know so well
We've never worked together before?
(Nana) Ah...
But we have had coffee together before.
[Laughing] Ah, well
He said he had something to ask.
Two?
[Junsu’s laughter]
(Edited) Ah, that’s too much
It's an obvious trick.
Oh, if it's about the company, you'll ask me.
You must be crazy, what is the age difference?
Uh, no.
It wasn't really like that.
So what did you ask?
Oh, that's...
You asked about the team leader.
[light music]
- Me?
- (Nana) Yes
[Interesting music]
[Keyboard operation sound]
(Shinwon) Team leader Baek Soo-jeong
I have a good place to work.
Are you thinking of changing jobs...
[Makes a yuck sound]
[sigh]
[Relaxing sigh]
[Notification sound]
Hey, sir, I'm surprised, sir...
work, yes
(Edited) Director Kim, do you have time?
[Car horn sounds loud]
(Seokhee) Yes
(Main cast) Team leader Baek Soo-jeong?
(Nana) Oh, you got off work first.
- Goodbye.
- (Junsu, Seokhee) Goodbye
(Junsu) No, actually, the team leader
Aren’t you interested in the manager?
[Thumping sound effect]
(Nana) Oh, no way
(Junsu) No, I have to leave work
There's no need to meet separately.
[Exciting music]
[Rewind sound effect]
[ding sound effect]
[Employees scream in shock]
What did you just say?
Which one?
Who is Team Leader Baek interested in?
No, who did you go to meet?
(Junsu) That, Design Department Manager Kim Shin-won?
(Main role) Assistant Manager Yang Junsu!
(Junsu) Yes...
Top button is undone
straight and neat
Go ahead and do it
[Humorous sound effects]
(Junsu) Thank you!
- (Nana) Thank you
- (Seokhee) Thank you
[Awkward laughter]
[forced laughter]
(Edited) Just see it at work.
Why did you call me to the cafe?
It's a waste of time
Ah, that, ah...
From where and how
I have to say this...
Then can I speak first?
(Shinwon) Oh, of course, as much as you want, yes
Well, manager...
Are you interested in me?
(Juyeon) That’s right
A subordinate tells a rumor
I can't just watch as I get caught up in it.
That's why I go, that's why
[Interesting music]
I...
Wasn't it?
You're asking
Are you interested in me?
[Eye blinking sound effect]
(Shinwon) Uh...
If you say there is no
It's probably a lie
But that interest
It's not a rational interest.
(Edited) Oh, what can I say, of course not.
Because I was close to the previous head of the department.
You're not out of spite, are you?
[upbeat music]
Or is it the head of the pre-war headquarters?
Or Director Jeon Jeon-jeon?
- (Identity) Yes?
- (Edited) Unless that's the case
In the design room
What do you need to check on me?
Oh, that, that
I think you've made a huge misunderstanding...
(Edited) The excuse is okay.
Don't investigate people in a shameful manner.
If you have any complaints, please come to us directly.
Don't bother people around you
Well then, that's it
[Shinwon’s embarrassed exclamation]
Wait a minute, I have something to say too.
What is it?
(Shinwon) Well, that’s over there...
Under Ban, Ban Joo-yeon, General Manager
Are you going to stay?
Why are you curious about that?
[Shinwon’s embarrassed groan]
Are you going to kick me out?
No, no, that can't be possible.
Well, uh, I mean...
(Shinwon) Uh, that means that I...
What, what was he trying to say...
[Sujeong’s frustrated sigh]
Oh, please come in.
[Door bell sounds]
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[Interesting music]
[sigh]
no
There's no way you can't see people like that.
[Sparkling sound effect]
[Soft music]
(Juyeon) Oh, no!
[Exciting music]
[Sound of door closing]
[Doorbell sounds]
(Wonseop) Ah, who else is there tonight...
(Sujeong) Okay, Dad, sit down.
[Tense sound effect]
[Exciting music]
(Edited) What kind of contract is this again?
Isn’t there something to write about?
It's not like that.
(Edited) Ah...
Eat it first
Eggs again today
It must be very tasty.
I'm still in the evening
(Juyeon) Instead, Baek Soo-jeong’s life
I'm here to give you some important advice.
My life?
Of course, construction classification is important.
(Juyeon) But the life of a subordinate
Just watching you fall into the abyss
I don't think it's my boss's duty.
Yes?
[humorous music]
(Juyeon) Read it
Are you here to recommend comic books?
(Edited) No matter how much, not me
I know there's no one to talk to like this, but
(Juyeon) There
If you look there
Why you shouldn't fall for a playboy
Well explained
I heard that my first love was also scammed by a scammer.
To the playboy
It can't happen again, can it?
What is that all of a sudden...
To Director Shinwon Kim
Something I'm rationally interested in
I know everything
Me?
Isn't it?
It's not
Then why
Did you meet separately at a cafe after work?
How did you know?
I happened to pass by and saw it
- (Edited) Ah...
- (Juyeon) I’m disappointed.
Even Baek Soo-jeong fell in love with that human charm.
I didn't know I was deluded
Smile and be kind
That kind of charm with good manners?
Soo-jeong Baek is like that too.
Is it good?
No, I don't like that.
(Edit) Wouldn’t it be better to just do that to me?
A bit clumsy and clumsy
I guess so.
Because love is unique
Then, I am interested in Director Kim Shin-won...
No, I'm not interested
They said they were investigating my background.
I met you to argue.
[Interesting music]
Background investigation?
[Sighing] Here and there
Looks like he was trying to find out my weakness.
(Juyeon) Ah...
[Slight moan]
[sigh]
Oishi, no
It's delicious
[Juyeon sighs]
(Juyeon) Who am I?
Let's eat
[Sound of car door opening]
[Sound of car door closing]
(Edited) Anyway, I'll have fun reading it
I don't have any chance of being bullied by a cheater.
It was rude late at night.
Please tell your father I'm sorry too.
yes
(Edited) But
I told Director Kim Shin-won
What were you going to do if you were really interested?
If you say it doesn't matter if you're a flirt,
that interest
I have to keep ripping it off until it disappears.
Why?
Because of his duty as a boss?
(Juyeon) Just
Because I don't like it
[Calm music]
Then let's go
(Subin) Sister
Who are you just now?
You don’t have to know, Mr...
[Interesting music]
(Subin) Isn’t 6,000 won cheap?
But now department stores will sell comics too?
Oh, not that.
(Wonseop) Hey, hey, hey
If it's not like that, then what?
Why did he come to my house again, huh?
No matter how much of a core talent you are,
Even paying my hospitalization fee wasn’t enough, huh?
This keeps coming up late at night
Well, I guess
[clears cough awkwardly]
The general manager told you
You don’t have any other intentions, right?
[Soobin bursts out laughing]
(Subin) Dad, I really heard it recently.
The funniest of all gags
No, my dad too
Are you Inverted Father?
A man likes his older sister
Hey Baek Soobin
(Soobin) No, he’s young and tall.
A man who drives a nice car
Ah, what do you like, sister?
[Soobin’s laughter]
[Slightly stirring sound effect]
[train horn sound effect]
- No...
- (Edited) Ah!
stop fussing
If you don't want to break your head
(Soobin) Uh...
(Edited) Put the cup away!
Look look
[Sound of door opening]
How can you have other thoughts like that, Dad?
[Sound of door closing]
Hey, somewhere else
Couldn’t it be a little different?
I guess not?
(In-kyung) Today, Director
You have an external schedule
I will do it for you
From the list of food hall stores
Strong Ranch is gone
Happy milk was included.
Is this something that was changed by the sales team?
yes
I think a contract with Strong Ranch is impossible.
I changed it
You can't miss that place.
Recently, it got a lot of attention by word of mouth.
Any other department store
It's a brand that doesn't deliver.
(Edited) To differentiate the food hall
It is a must to enter the store
(Hyeju) Who doesn’t know that?
I tried to persuade you
Even if you give me 10 billion
It is not possible to enter department stores.
Is that the company policy?
Ah, I need a little more persuasion...
(Hyeju) Easier said than done
What is the sales team just doing?
A company that doesn't even sit at the negotiating table at all
How can I persuade you?
if you can
Would you like Team Leader Baek Soo-jeong to try it?
[Meaningful music]
Happy Milk too
It is a sufficiently competitive brand.
Okay
Because reality is also important.
(In-kyung) To the head of the department:
I will report it like this.
Okay then next
Are you really planning on going in person?
Oh, you never know.
Tomorrow is the weekend too
Okay, good luck.
(Sujeong) [Laughing] Yes
[Exciting music]
[Applause from caddies and executives]
(Executives) Good shot, good shot
(Executive 1) Oh, thank you for your hard work.
- (Executive 2) Thank you for your hard work.
- (In-kyung) Thank you for your hard work.
Why do you play golf like that?
I don't know if I like it
If it weren't for the chairman
I wouldn't have come to a place like this.
Aside from that...
[Fanfare sound effect]
Congratulations on the hole in one
What should I do, I'm the accompanist
(Juyeon) I can’t do what I can’t do
Ah, from the list you sent me yesterday
Why was Strong Ranch missing?
This is a decision made by the sales team.
Kanghan Ranch opens in a department store
I don't even consider it.
So, at our department store
It will have a huge impact when it opens.
(Juyeon) Tell me to try to persuade you somehow.
Because there is still time
(In-kyung) Anyway, today, Team Leader Baek Soo-jeong
I went to persuade him in person.
Alone?
I can't guarantee the results though
It will be resolved soon.
[lively music]
[light laughter]
[Sound of bus door opening]
[Card recognition sound]
(Sujeong) Ah, I’ll listen as far as I can.
[Sound of bus door closing]
No, no, this is heavy.
Do I have to go to the ranch up there?
Oh, it's heavy, so I'll lift it for you.
(CEO Ahn) [Laughing] Oh my
The young woman is also kind.
thank you
But this far away
Why did you come alone?
Ah, I came to the ranch, Strong Ranch.
[CEO Ahn’s puzzled groan]
(Edited) The ice cream here is really delicious.
But they only sell it here
I came here once to see the ranch.
Oh my, I have a lot of time.
No, what kind of ice cream should I get?
Did you come this far?
Oh, I see.
So that people can eat easily
Somewhere like a department store
It would be great to open a store.
(Edited) Why, what’s delicious?
They say the more you share, the better it tastes.
[light laughter]
(CEO Ahn) Huh?
[Interesting music]
Why, why are you like that?
Give it to me
(Representative Ahn) That bag
Give me this, give me, give me this
(Edited) I guess you noticed, CEO.
(Representative Ahn) Oh
[CEO Ahn’s light smile]
Which company is it from?
Is it Kayu or Yongseong?
Yongseong Department Store
I came from the planning team.
It's called Baeksujeong.
Thank you very much
No, I don't have anything to ask for.
Something like Yongseong
Do you know how to sell our products?
(CEO Ahn) What I hate the most is
He's a tycoon who gets rich from his own belly, huh?
that tycoon
Ah, so here's our suggestion...
[Sound of car door opening]
[Exciting music]
Is this Representative Ahn?
(CEO Ahn) Uh...
What is this again?
[CEO Ahn’s light smile]
Oh, look at your outfit.
I don't think you're just an ordinary employee, right?
[Laughing] Of course, after Yongseong...
I grew up under the support of Yongseong.
[Squeaking sound effect]
This is my younger brother
[humorous music]
This master?
[Sujeong’s awkward laughter]
(Edited) You misunderstood because of the car and clothes.
[Sujeong’s shy smile]
His job is a driver.
These are all other people’s cars and other people’s clothes.
They said it was nearby
Did you come all the way here to see your sister?
[Sujeong’s awkward laughter]
That's good, CEO.
I'll give you a ride to the ranch.
- Get in.
- (CEO Ahn) No, give me this baggage.
[Sound of car door opening]
Ah, this, this, this, this...
(Edited) I already put it inside.
CEO, get on quickly.
[CEO Ahn’s embarrassed groan]
Carefully, now, carefully
What are you doing? Why don’t you come quickly?
[light laughter]
[Sound of car door closing]
[absurd gasping sound]
What is it?
[Cow crying sound effect]
(Edited) Why on earth did you come all the way here?
Go ahead, I'll take care of it.
[The sound of a cow mooing is heard]
(Juyeon) Are you that dissatisfied with my coming?
No, Representative Ahn
A chaebol like the general manager
I mean, you just hate it.
Then what about Team Leader Baek alone?
We'll see how well he does.
People came to help
Are you here to help?
no, what
Nothing to be too impressed with
my abilities now
Are you saying you came because you were suspicious?
Is it because you don’t trust me because you’re afraid you won’t be able to do it alone?
I believe it
You'll do well
But?
(Juyeon) Still, I struggle alone
Isn’t it a bit difficult?
lonely and
[Soft music]
It's okay if you don't need it
Okay, let’s persuade together.
(Edited) Instead, just pretend to be your younger brother.
Don't show that you're a chaebol
Why are you my younger brother?
So what do you say?
Friends are strange
My boyfriend is even weirder
Why is that strange?
(Edited) Ah, that’s strange.
Just by looking at it, you can see how big the age difference is.
Oh, maybe your boyfriend is younger.
Ah, if you think about it that way
Isn’t it weirder that your boss is younger?
Well, don't say nonsense.
Please find a representative quickly.
Earlier...
(Sujeong) You went that way earlier.
Why is it like that, it keeps confusing people?
What doesn't make sense?
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
[Sujeong’s light smile]
[bell sound]
[Sujeong’s shy smile]
What is this again?
Representative!
(CEO Ahn) Oh, it worked out well.
- CEO
- (Representative Ahn) Huh?
what's this?
Kid...
Ouch, what is it, ooh!
(Edited) Ah, let’s go together.
[The sound of a cow mooing is heard]
[Sigh of Sujeong]
(Edit) It's not easy.
(Juyeon) That’s enough.
If it continues like this
It only makes us look funny.
no
It's already getting ridiculous
Refusing to enter a store because you belong to a conglomerate?
I started with a business mindset.
(Edited) Ha, just one time
Try convincing me one more time, okay?
[Soft music]
It's the last time
That's right
[The sound of a cow mooing is heard]
[Happy laughter]
CEO
(Representative Ahn) Oh my, oh my, oh my
Wow, I’m surprised.
No, these people really
Did you plan to make someone faint?
Oh, get out of here!
- Oh, I can't turn it off, CEO.
- (Representative Ahn) Huh?
(Edited) After looking around the ranch,
I can't give up anymore
Many people use Strong Ranch products.
I wish I knew
(CEO Ahn) No, well I don’t know, I don’t know.
Go, go
- Hurry up, go.
- No, CEO, I'm serious.
(Edited) Let’s talk for a moment...
(CEO Ahn) No, well
I said I have nothing to talk about, so get the hell out of here.
- No, get out, get out, get out.
- (Edited) No, just talking... [Humorous sound effect]
(Juyeon) No, over there!
[Juyeon’s startled scream]
[humorous music]
[Cow crying]
(CEO Ahn) Oh my, it’s really amazing.
No, these people
Come to someone's workplace and put on a show
Put on a very raw show
[Cow crying]
[Door bell sounds]
It's not open yet
(Hajin) Huh?
What are you doing at this time?
I came to meet Mr. Hajin.
Me?
Oh, that's that, uh, over there, over there
Separating two people
I feel like I'm going to fail
(Shinwon) Take some action
I think I need to stand up a little bit.
(Hajin) Uh, contact me and come.
I was just about to go to the market.
Really?
Then let's go together
We can talk about it, right?
Shall we go?
[Soft music]
(Shinwon) Oh
As expected
You liked internet novels
Somehow
The personal message was just my style.
I also saw this often in the military.
- That in the military?
- (Shinwon) Yes
Anything in it is fun.
Except training
[Shinwon and Hajin laugh]
What about games? Are you still doing it these days?
(Hajin) Well, sometimes
I used to do this often before I opened the store.
I'm not good at it these days because I don't have time.
Moonpajang’s seat too
I handed it over to another kid.
But why do you keep asking about me?
(Hajin) Juyeon and Sujeong
Aren’t you here to talk?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, that's right, that's what I came to talk about, yeah
Ah, what should I do with these two people?
(ID) Yo?
[Hajin sighs]
(Hajin) We met by chance at a company.
(Shinwon) But I’m glad
Because we don’t have anything to meet on the weekend.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Hajin) Oh, but it’s the weekend and you have no plans?
Can I stay here like this?
I think there are a lot of people looking for it.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
No, promise, yeah
[Sound of night birds and insects]
Do you always carry the same clothes with you?
It's basic.
Unlike others who are not prepared
[absurd gasping sound]
(Juyeon) But the house is so...
(Representative Ahn) Oh, if you change your clothes, you can sit down.
What are you doing?
(Juyeon) CEO
Is this really the CEO’s house?
I have doubts about the financial condition of Kanghan Ranch.
(Representative Ahn) Why? What do you suspect?
Hey, banjuyeon!
(Sujeong) Would you like to get spanked once?
[Humorous sound effects]
[light music]
Butt?
Donate all your savings
(Edited) So far, frugality has been used
What kind of disrespect is this to someone who has personally practiced it?
I apologize quickly
Rude...
No, but if you are the CEO
(Juyeon) A house better than this
Shouldn’t you buy it?
You've worked hard all this time.
(Representative Ahn) Why? What's wrong with this house?
It's okay if I live alone without any problems.
Don't talk nonsense
Come on sit down and eat some food
Why do you spank my butt?
Where is my ass, where is my ass...
(Edited) Rice...
There are a lot
(Representative Ahn) Why are there so many of these?
That's why you're so skinny
Eat that and eat some more
- (Edited) Yes
- (Representative Ahn) Try some of this too.
This is a waste of time
Although it is a bit bitter, it tastes good.
I dug it up myself from that field.
(Edited) Yes...
[Sujeong’s awkward laughter]
[Sujeong’s embarrassed groan]
[Humorous sound effects]
Why?
Don't you eat it?
older sister
[humorous music]
(Edited) Huh?
Oh, did you call me?
The CEO is removing the cans from the field.
(Juyeon) You’re not really rejecting me, are you?
rudely
[Awkward laughter]
No
[light laughter]
Well then
(Juyeon) Eat a lot, sister
You eat a lot too, little brother.
(Sujeong) You also eat bitter food well.
Thanks, Nu, me
Very friendly, huh?
[Sujeong’s awkward laughter]
[Juyeon’s light smile]
[telephone ringing sound]
(CEO Ahn) Ah, yes, yes
Oh yeah, my baby
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Ah, then, Grandma is okay.
Everything is good
[Tap sound effect]
So, did you eat?
[Interesting music]
Okay, okay, okay.
Hang up, okay, let's hang up, uh
I guess this is contact with the grandson?
(CEO Ahn) Yes
[CEO Ahn’s happy laughter]
my child really likes me
I recently took the bar exam
I passed the exam and am now working.
I got a call saying I'm leaving work now.
Who do you look like and you're so smart?
I guess you look like the CEO.
(CEO Ahn) Huh?
[laughter heartily]
Is that so?
[Happy laughter]
(Edited) You must be very proud.
I'm not proud
Well, I was born prematurely.
I was in a lot of pain.
(Representative Ahn) If you just grow up healthy,
Thank you
When did my baby get so big?
[Sighing] People
It's just a plight for me to live like this.
Make money and do good things for others
They say they will order it.
I don't do that for nothing
A good world for our children to live in
[Calm music]
That's because I want to create that kind of society.
Not just a grandmother who makes a lot of money
Because I want to be a proud grandmother
The CEO’s grandson is
You must be happy
Being loved so much by my grandmother
[Happy laughter]
So
(Edited) Yongseong Department Store
Let’s work together, CEO.
Oh my, this is so awful.
(CEO Ahn) No, he said he was just an ordinary employee.
How much do you want to be paid?
[Embarrassed laughter]
Oh, it's not like that.
Anyone would come in there anyway.
(Edited) If possible, not someone else.
I hope the CEO makes a lot of money
It's because I like it
The representative’s good influence
It would be nice if it got bigger
I also want to help you, Mr.
[CEO Ahn’s light smile]
persistent, persistent
(CEO Ahn) Oh, hurry up and eat.
Eat and talk
Then if you eat all of this
Are you listening to me?
[CEO Ahn’s response]
[light laughter]
[Sujeong’s satisfied moan]
(Sujeong) Little brother, mix it and eat it.
[Sujeong’s light smile]
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
(Edited) This...
Are you developing a new product?
Can I try it?
(CEO Ahn) Oh, whatever.
(Edited) Huh?
what's this?
Is this yogurt?
This will be a big hit when it's released
Hey, do you want to drink it too?
[Sound of pouring drinks]
Now
Drink it all the time, drink it all the time
Try the new product from Kanghan Ranch
You should feel very honored.
It's alcohol
[light music]
(CEO Ahn) Yes, that’s the makgeolli I made.
Go to the mineral spring up there
I made it by drawing water myself.
It tastes good, right?
It seems stupid
Bar...
What an idiot, this is rude to my sister.
(Juyeon) Is it time to shout out loud?
How are you going to get home, sister?
[Interesting music]
No, just as it came.
Just take the bus
(Representative Ahn) Um...
If you were going to go, you should have gone a long time ago.
All the buses were cut off
I guess I should call the driver.
(CEO Ahn) Article?
No, you're not the driver?
Oh, I meant the substitute driver.
(Representative Ahn) Representation from here to Seoul?
Can't you?
[CEO Ahn clicks his tongue]
Oh my, I live under a father who runs a hardware store.
Taking care of my sick mother
Pay off all your debt, okay?
(CEO Ahn) I was trying to repay the house loan.
Didn't you say you were having a hard time?
But do you think your younger brother has suffered less?
[Embarrassed laughter]
You pretended not to listen to me
Well, it's because he's still young.
(Edited) He’s 5 years younger than me.
Well, compared to me, he's a complete kid.
- (Representative Ahn) Huh?
- (Edited) Well, um
- Kid?
- (Edited) Write!
How much is the agency fee from here to Seoul?
Why don't you throw some money on the street?
No, then what are you going to do?
older sister
Well... what should I do?
(Representative Ahn) What should I do?
I should go to sleep
[Grass bugs and howling all night long]
(Edited) The potatoes were cooked very well.
Director
Don’t you treat me like your younger brother anymore?
why? Do you want to call me sister again?
(Sujeong) It suits you so well
I thought he was really my younger brother
Ah, I'm sorry it happened like this.
So just go
[laughter]
Is that an apple?
Sweeten it to the general manager’s taste.
It would be perfect, right?
[Sound of pouring makgeolli]
(Edited) I came here to take a day off today.
Will you think about it?
The air is nice and the stars are pretty.
It was just something I said.
Because I'm doing this
I feel like I'm really resting.
I couldn't even go on vacation this year because I was working.
Why are you working so hard?
whatever
[Calm music]
When I was young
Hanging upside down on an iron bar
Because you liked it?
But a passing man
Girls play rough like that
It's not possible.
(Edited) With a young heart
That's so annoying and ridiculous
I played harder like that.
Another day I went to school
The teacher wants me to give up being class president.
Because my mom doesn't care
I don't think it will work
Where is that?
The class president's job is his own.
So
As they wish
Determine my limits
I hate being judged.
So if you say no
I worked harder
tenaciously
(Edited) That I can do it
Feeling like I want to be recognized
Do you know what it is?
I know
To whom exactly
It's not something that needs to be acknowledged, but
I guess it's just personality
(Sujeong) I want to be good at everything
I can't stand being ignored
that kind of personality
[Calm music - continued]
[Embarrassed laughter]
Me too
(Juyeon) I want to be recognized
I want to do well
I can't stand being ignored
[Laughs slightly]
Why are you smiling?
(Edited) The head of the department and I
I thought it looked similar
It's funny, it doesn't make sense.
Nothing makes sense
(Juyeon) Because there is another similarity
first love
To me too
twice again
This is someone I don't want to meet.
If that person
Me as I am
I thought he would admit it
It was the worst
Between comrades who had the worst first love
Should I salt it?
(Edited) Salty
[Sound of clinking glasses]
[bright music]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Wait a minute
(Sujeong) Uh, sister
I'm on a business trip to Gangwon-do, with the head of the department.
Hey, what is a man
I heard you’re the same age as Soobin Baek.
Will I look like a man?
[light music]
(Hajin) Still, with the head of the department
Aren't we being too friendly?
So why not?
It’s better than the general manager killer.
(Hajin) No, I
Even if the truth is uncomfortable for you
I'm afraid you'll find out
An inconvenient truth?
Well, that...
Are you a chaebol?
(Hajin) What if there is corruption or something like that?
Can you put up with your personality?
Then things really get bigger, you
Write, sister, are you bored?
Are you paying too much attention to not fitting in?
[Sighing] I don’t know.
you said clearly
I don’t feel like the head of the department is a man.
(Edited) Huh?
uh
Okay, good work.
Why is this sister like this?
It's strange
(Edited) Are you sleeping?
If I drink alcohol, I fall asleep.
Director, go in and sleep.
Yes?
Director
[Calm music]
offended
No, I...
To wake you up
Why do you keep ignoring people?
When am I?
[Calm music]
Even if this happens
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
Doesn't he look like a man?
[Exciting music]
[Music: ‘He’s a Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
(Edited) Namjoo’s psychology
I just can't understand it
(Juyeon) Shall we work together as comrades?
It happened last night
Are you just going to move on like this?
(Juyeon) Let’s just overlook that kind of mistake.
(Edited) Crazy, such a mistake
Should I just move on?
Are you on a blind date?
(Juyeon) Is it real?
(Edited) Why are you curious about that?
(Jihoo) Sujeong!
(Edit) I was worried because they said I was going on a blind date.
(Juyeon) I don’t care
[People cheering]
Why me?
Why don't I look like a man?